myintrasite.com 2010-06-12

# Lifestyles

Lifestyles® International Holdings Corporation Online Privacy Statement
  Lifestyles is committed to respecting your privacy and safeguarding your personal information when
  accessing www.lifestyles.net and/or any associated affiliate sites from Lifestyles (the “Site”). As part
  of this commitment to you, we want you to be informed regarding the information that may be
  collected from you when visiting our websites, how your personal information is being used and
  secured, and how you may contact us to update or edit your personal information. Lifestyles
  operates in compliance with the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA).
  Collection of Personal Information
  Lifestyles collects personal information when you:
     • Purchase Lifestyles products or services through the website;
     • Request Lifestyles e-mail communications;
     • Request an Independent Distributor or local office to contact you;
     • Provide us with feedback or suggestions.
  To access online ordering through our websites, submitting online applications, or to receive e-mail
  communications, we collect contact information such as your name, address, telephone number, and
  may also collect certain optional demographic information, such as your date of birth and gender. To
  purchase Lifestyles products or services through our websites, we collect your credit card information
  and address for shipping, which is properly secured as outlined in the security portion of the Lifestyles
  privacy act.
  Use of Personal Information
  The personal information you provide us when you access Lifestyles websites, or consent to
  receiving e-mail communications, is used to identify who you are and to provide you with the
  information you have requested. This may include information regarding Lifestyles products, our
  business opportunity, local incentives or promotions, website features, and information about
  corporate or local events. Any credit card and shipping address information you provide is used solely
  to process any orders you place for Lifestyles products offered through the website or for
  communication purposes from Lifestyles exclusively. Survey and feedback information you provide
  may be used to address your needs such as to understand your product preferences and to
  determine how Lifestyles products, services and websites can be improved.
  Security of Personal Information
  Lifestyles operates secure data networks protected by password and industry standard firewalls. We
  are committed to protecting your sensitive information by securing it from unauthorized access, use or
  disclosure through SSL encryption software. We will maintain strict confidentiality of all personal
  information collected, and will only disclose such information to Lifestyles employees and affiliate
  offices for internal purposes only those who may require such information for the purposes outlined in
  the use the Lifestyles privacy policy.

Lifestyles® International Holdings Corporation Online Privacy Statement
  Disclosure of Personal Information
  In compliance with the Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (FIPPA) as
  expressly set out in this privacy statement, we will not sell, transfer or otherwise disclose any of your
  personal information to any third party without your prior knowledge and consent, except where
  breach of contract, legality issues regarding violation of policies and procedures, or otherwise
  required by law.
  Consent
  Lifestyles respects your online privacy. By accessing our websites, you consent to the collection and
  use of this information by Lifestyles in a manner consistent with the guidelines stated in this online
  privacy statement.
  Cookies
  Cookies are small pieces of information that may be stored on your computer hard drive for ease of
  recognizing your information when you return our website or to provide you with a user friendly
  experience. Lifestyles cookies do not contain any sensitive information such as legal name or credit
  card information. However, we cannot control or be responsible for third parties using cookies and the
  distribution of the information thereof. Most web browsers allow you to erase or block cookies,
  however please note that you may not be able to access certain areas of our websites, or experience
  the true benefits of Lifestyles when disabling cookies from your web browser.
  Links to Lifestyles Independent Distributor PBC and the Distributor Personal websites
  This online privacy statement applies to Lifestyles International Holdings Corporation and its affiliate
  offices world wide. Lifestyles Independent Distributors may also operate their own websites through
  their Personal Business Center (PBC) and their Distributor Personal Web Sites. Independent Distributor
  websites in the Lifestyles Personal Business Center are by Lifestyles, and although we strictly enforce our
  online privacy policy, each Independent Distributor is liable for their own personal websites and the collection
  and usage of personal information.
  Third Party Websites
  Lifestyles websites may include links to other third party websites. As these linked sites have
  separate and independent privacy policies and practices, we cannot assume responsibility or liability
  for the manner in which the organizations collect, use or disclose and otherwise treat your personal
  information.

Lifestyles® International Holdings Corporation Online Privacy Statement
  Revisions to the Lifestyles Privacy Policy
  This privacy statement is effective October 14, 2009. Lifestyles reserves the right to modify or revise
  this privacy policy at any time and will become effective immediately upon notice. Changes to this
  privacy policy may be provided to you through several forms of communication, including posting the
  most recent version on our websites.
  Contact Us
  If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement or wish to contact us to update
  your personal information, please e-mail Customer Service at canada@lifestyles.net
